Guide to the College of Engineering, Technology, and Architecture records ARCH175
University of Hartford Archives & Special Collections
College of Engineering, Technology, and Architecture records
2001-2009
University of Hartford Archives & Special Collections
University of Hartford. College of Engineering, Technology, and Architecture
ARCH175
1.67 Linear Feet (4 containers)
This collection consists of the records of the College of Engineering, Technology, and Architecture (CETA) at the University of Hartford.
Conditions Governing Access
The collection is open to all researchers.
Scope and Contents
At this time, the majority of the collection consists of records pertaining to the creation of the University High School of Science and Engineering. This includes designs for the physical space, as well as plans for, and evaluations of, the curriculum and operations of the school. The remainder of the collection is rather small and currently includes only a small number of photographs and a subject file pertaining to CETA.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into three series: I. University High School of Science and Engineering, II. Photographs, and III. Subject Files.
Magnet schools; University High School of Science and Engineering (Hartford, Conn.); Hartford Public Schools (Hartford, Conn.)
- University High School of Science and Engineering, 2001-2009
  - Documents, 2001; 2006-2008 (Box UHSSE 1, Folder 1)
  - Organizing Documents, 2001-2005 (Box UHSSE 1, Folder 2-4)
  - Planning, 2003 (Box UHSSE 1, Folder 5)
  - Organizing Minutes, 2003-2004 (Box UHSSE 1, Folder 6-7)
  - Coordinating Council, 2003-2005 (Box UHSSE 2, Folder 1-2)
  - Site Planning Committee, 2004-2005 (Box UHSSE 2, Folder 3)
  - Woodrow Wilson Foundation (W.W.F), 2004-2005 (Box UHSSE 2, Folder 4)
  - Pre-Construction I, 2006 (Box UHSSE 2, Folder 5-6)
  - Pre-Construction II, 2006 (Box UHSSE 2, Folder 7, Box UHSSE 3, Folder 1)
  - Pre-Construction III, 2006-2007 (Box UHSSE 3, Folder 2-3)
  - Construction I, 2007-2008 (Box UHSSE 3, Folder 4-6)
  - Hartford School Building Committee I, 2008 (Box UHSSE 4, Folder 1-3)
  - Construction II, 2009 (Box UHSSE 4, Folder 4)
  - Hartford School Building Committee II, 2009 (Box UHSSE 4, Folder 5-6)
- Photographs, undated (Box UHSSE 4, Folder 7)
- Subject Files, 2005
  - A Celebration of our History and Legacy, 2005 Jun 9 (Box UHSSE 4, Folder 8)